Ready, set, go, we step over the goal line
isse nou se de fumikomu gourain
Still, we don't know anything at all
bokura wa nanimo nanimo mada shiranu
We look back as we pass the line, and it's already gone
issen koete furikaeruto mou nai
Still, we don't know anything at all
bokura wa nanimo nanimo mada shiranu
Fiercely, fiercely we move on
udatte udatte udatteku
Drenched in glistening sweat
kirameku ase ga koboreru no sa
There probably were a lot of things we didn't remember
oboetenai koto mo takusan atta darou
Everyone was just a silhouette
daremo kare mo shiruetto
Let's become adults,
daiji ni shitai mono motte otona ni naru nda
holding on to things we want to cherish
And let's keep on protecting them at all times
donna toki mo hanasazu ni mamori tsudzukeyou
Then someday...
soshitara itsu no hi ni ka
We'll be able to laugh at it all
nanimo kamo o waraerusa
Like the light and nimble dancing
hirari to hirari to matteru
Of leaves taking flight
konoha ga tonde yuku
As a Taijutsu User
(リー)シラ君には 忍術や幻術を扱う
スキルがほとんどない。
Shira has almost no skill for
ninjutsu or genjutsu...
(リー)シラ君は 僕と同じ
体術しかできない忍なんです。
Shira and I are alike...
We're shinobi who
can only perform taijutsu.
(セン)あんた 気づいてたのね。
So you knew.
(リー)昨日 彼と手合わせを
したときにわかりました。
I realized it yesterday
when we exchanged punches.
忍術や幻術を使える人たちには
わからないかもしれません。
Those who are skilled in ninjutsu
and genjutsu may not notice
とても繊細で特殊な
僕と似た感じがしたんです。
that slight, yet unique difference.
I sensed that he was like me.
(セン)そこまで
気づかれてるんなら話すわ。
Since you know that much,
let me explain.
砂隠れじゃ 先代の風影様まで➡
In Hidden Sand Village,
not even the previous Kazekage
シラのような人たちは
忍と認められなかったのよ。
would allow people like Shira
to become shinobi.
(リー)そんな！
シラ君ほどの体術使いでもですか？
But that's—! Even a great taijutsu user
like Shira?!
そうよ だからシラは
ついこの前までアカデミーにも行けず➡
That's right. That's why until just recently...
Shira wasn't allowed to attend the Academy
and was treated like an outsider.
SHINOBI ACADEMY
みんなから仲間外れにされてた。
((あっ。
(３人）あっ。
おいっ 忍術 使えないやつが
何見てんだよ！
Hey! What're you staring at?
You can't even use ninjutsu!
(シラ)うっ。
(向こう行け！
お前のダメダメがうつるだろ))
Go away! Your uselessness is contagious!
(セン)でも シラは諦めなかった。
But Shira refused to give up
and believed in himself.
自分を信じて。
((シラ : は～！
ふっ はっ でやっ！
ふっ はっ だっ…。
ふっ ふっ はっ…。
(ふっ はっ ふっ…))
(セン)ずっと一人で
体術を磨き続けた。
He kept training all by himself
and honed his taijutsu.
でも 時代は変わった。
Then, the times changed...
四代目 風影亡きあと➡
The seat was empty for a while
しばらく空席だった
五代目 風影の座に➡
after the Fourth Kazekage
passed away...
我愛羅様がおさまったのよ。
but eventually Lord Gaara
became the Fifth Kazekage.
以前の我愛羅様を知る人々は
里が恐ろしいことになると噂した。
Those who knew
Lord Gaara's past
spread rumors that
our village was doomed,
けど 実際は違ったわ。
but that wasn't the case.
我愛羅様は
人々の意見を聞き入れ➡
Lord Gaara was receptive
to other people's opinions...
次々と先代の因習を断ち切り
里の改革を進めたのよ。
and one by one, he did away with
the previous Kazekage's practices
and instituted reforms.
((ヨメ : あれが我愛羅様？
That's Lord Gaara?
ああ ガキの頃
一緒に遊んでたテマリの弟だ。
Yeah. He's the younger brother
of Temari,
the girl we used to play with
when we were kids.
(我愛羅)
あそこには砂防のための➡
What happened to the huge boulder
that was used to prevent sand erosion?
巨大岩があったはずだが？
そ それが…。
Well...
これを壊した者を呼べ。
Bring me the one
who destroyed this.
シラと言ったな。
Are you Shira?
あれは里を守るための
岩と知っていたはず。
You knew that boulder
was placed there
to protect Hidden Sand Village.
なぜ倒した？
Why did you destroy it?
申し訳ありません。
I am very sorry.
倒すつもりではありませんでした。
I had no intention of
destroying it.
あの岩は 私にとっても
大切な修業相手でした。
To me, that boulder was
an invaluable training partner.
修業で倒したというのか？
Are you saying you destroyed it
during training?
お前はアカデミーの
生徒ではないと聞いたが。
I was told you are not
a student at the Academy.
はい 私には 忍術や幻術のスキルが
ほとんどありません。
No.
I don't have any skills in
ninjutsu or genjutsu.
この里の決まりでは➡
According to the village rules,
私のような者が忍になることは
許されていないのです。
someone like me is unfit
to be a shinobi.
それで 一人で修業を
続けていたというのか…。
So you trained all by yourself?
おもしろい。
Interesting...
あの岩とお前と
どちらが価値があるのか➡
I want to see which
is more valuable...
見極めさせてもらおうか。
That boulder or you!
うぉ～！
見事なこぶしだ。
Your fist is splendid!
あっ 失礼しました。
Please forgive me!
アカデミーに行けないお前が
ここまで技を磨くには➡
I can't begin to imagine
the effort it took for you,
banned from the Academy, to hone
your skills to this level.
俺の想像もできない努力が
あったはずだ。
(我愛羅)先代が定めた決め事は
今をもって廃止する。
I hereby abolish the rule established
by my predecessor.
シラ 忍になれ。
Shira, you will be a shinobi.
俺は以前 木ノ葉で➡
I once met someone just
like you in Hidden Leaf Village.
お前と同じような者と
出会ったことがある。
うぉ～！
こっちですよ！
Over here!
うわっ！
(我愛羅)その者は たゆまぬ努力で
立派な忍となっている。
Through sheer perseverance,
he has become a fine shinobi.
(シラ お前なら その者にも劣らぬ
忍となろう))
Shira, I predict you will become
as good a shinobi as he.
それでシラは やっと忍に
なることができたのよ。
That's how Shira finally
became a shinobi.
我愛羅様は それだけじゃなく➡
Not only that...
シラの人柄を見込んで
自分の体術指南役に取り上げたわ。
Lord Gaara recognized
Shira's character and
chose him to be
his personal taijutsu coach.
風影の体術指南っていったら
大出世じゃないですか！
To be named the Kazekage's
taijutsu coach is a huge advancement!
でも それを快く思わない連中も
多くいるの。
But this displeased many.
(ネジ)ついこの前まで 自分より
下だと思っていたやつが➡
When someone who until just recently
was below your rank
大出世をとげれば
妬むやつも出てくる➡
attains great success,
people become jealous...
というわけか。
I understand now.
人の意識が変わるには
長い時間がかかる。
Changing people's perceptions
takes time.
そうか だからシラ君は
あんなことを…。
I see, so that's why Shira
said that to me...
((お前が何を感じたかは知らない。
I don't know what it is you sensed,
だが 生まれの不幸を
嘆いても意味などない。
but dwelling on the misfortunes
of birth is meaningless.
(その不幸を含めて
人生はひとつしかないからな))
Because, for all one's flaws
and suffering, we have just one life.
《リー : シラ君 キミは
すごい努力をしてきた。
Shira, you persevered
so much, and yet...
なのに キミをこんなにした連中を
僕は許せない！》
I'll never forgive the ones
who did this to you!
(テンテン)リー！
Lee!
あのバカ！ まさか
さっきの連中を…。
That idiot... Don't tell me he's going to...
《チャクラを上手く使えず
ずっとバカにされ続けて…》
I wasn't good at using
my chakra...
so everyone belittled me...
((ハハッ！ バ～カ！ お前が忍者に
なれるわけねえだろ！
Stupid! There's no way
you'll become a ninja!
だいたい 忍術使えないやつが
忍者になれるわけねえじゃん。
There's no way a chump
who can't even use ninjutsu
can become a ninja!
なぁ？
なれます！
Yes, I will!
っていうかよ 人並み以下の
体術以外 何もできねえお前が➡
Whatever...
The fact that you're even in
the academy is nonsense.
この忍術アカデミーにいること自体
ナンセンスなんだぜ。
You don’t have ninjutsu
or genjutsu skills,
and your taijutsu is below average!
ヘッ お前ここで
何て呼ばれてっか知ってっか？
Do you know what
everyone calls you here?
あっ あ～！
(ガイ)ついに今日から
お前たちも下忍になった。
All right, as of today,
you're all genin.
そこで お前たちの目指すものを
聞いてみたい。
So I'd like to know what it is
you're all aiming for!
答えたくない。
先生！
I don't want to answer...
Sensei!
たとえ忍術や幻術は
使えなくても➡
I'd like to prove that I can
become a respectable shinobi
立派な忍者になれることを
証明したいんです。
even though I can't use
ninjutsu or genjutsu!
それが 僕のすべてです。
That would mean everything to me!
フッ。
キミ！ 何がおかしい！
Hey! What's so funny?!
お前 忍術も幻術も使えない
って時点で 忍者じゃないだろ。
If you can't use ninjutsu
or genjutsu,
you're already out as a ninja.
(リー)うわぁ！
(テンテン)リー！ ほんとあんたってば
懲りないんだから。
Lee, you just won't learn
your lesson, will you?
勝てっこないでしょ。
ネジは あんたと違って➡
There's no way you can win.
Unlike you, Neji is...
天才なんだから。
... a genius.
無駄だよ リー。
いかに努力したところで➡
It’s useless, Lee...
No matter how much effort
you make,
お前に 俺は倒せない。
これは 決まっていることだ。
there's no way you can
take me down.
That’s just fact.
くっ…。
ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！
Yes! Yes! Yes!
腕立て 500回
連続でできなければ➡
If I can't do 500 push-ups,
縄跳び 1,200回 二重跳びで！
I'll jump rope
and do 1200 double unders!
1,200回 できなかったら
丸太蹴り 2,000回！
If I can't do that,
I'll log kick 2000 times!
1,116… 1,117！
1116...1117...
あっ！
くっ… うぅ…。
リーよ もう休憩か？
Lee! Are you taking
a break already?
何の用ですか？ ガイ先生。
What is it, Guy Sensei?
この前の任務での失敗なら
もう詫びたはずです。
If it's about my blunder during
the recent mission,
I believe I have already apologized!
確かに… お前は ネジとは違う。
Lee, it's true you're different
from Neji.
忍術や幻術の天才でもなければ
体術の天才でもない。
You have no ninjutsu
or genjutsu skills,
and you're no taijutsu expert either...
けどなぁ リー。
But Lee...
お前も ネジをこえる力を…。
You have powers
that can exceed Neji's...
その可能性を秘めてる
天才なんだぞ。
You're a genius with
hidden potential.
気休めなら やめてください。
If you're trying to
make me feel better, please stop.
気休めでもなんでもない。
I'm not trying to make you feel better
or anything!
なぜなら リー お前は努力の天才だ。
あっ！
The reason is that you are...
a genius of hard work!
(自分を信じないやつなんかに
努力する価値はない！))
There's no point in
working hard
if you don't believe in yourself!
《僕も ずっと自分を信じて
努力してきました。
I hung in there because
I believe in myself.
シラ君 キミは まるで
もう一人の僕じゃないですか！
Shira... You're just like me!
いや アカデミーに行けなかったキミは➡
In fact, since you weren't able
to attend the Academy,
僕以上の思いで
修業を続けてきたはず。
you must have trained
much harder than me!
その努力を侮辱した人は
僕が絶対に許さない！》
I won't forgive the ones who
were contemptuous of your efforts!
くっ…。
これは！
This is—!
ったく！
お前たちが逃げ出さなきゃ➡
Damn it...
If you guys hadn't run off,
we could've obtained a scroll.
巻物を手に入れられたのにな！
あの白眼の班は シラが いちばん
警戒していたやつだ。
That team with the Byakugan user
is the one Shira warned us about.
敬遠するにこしたことはない。
チッ！
Better safe than sorry.
それより あいつらは
追いついてこないだろうな？
By the way, they're not coming
after us, are they?
ありったけの起爆札を
使っちまったが➡
I used all those Paper Bombs,
あの辺りは もともと
地下空洞の多い場所だからな。
and that area has a lot
of underground caverns...
思ったより でかい崖ができた。
The explosions created
a steeper cliff than I expected.
あれを避けてくるには
時間がかかる。
It'll take them a while
to make their way across.
(リー)果たして そうでしょうか？
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
誰だ？
Who's there?!
木ノ葉の美しき碧き野獣 ロック・リー！
The handsome blue beast of
the Hidden Leaf, Rock Lee!
お前は さっきの！
You're that guy from earlier!
キミたちが シラ君にしたことは
許せません！
What you did to Shira
is unforgivable!
シラ君に謝ってください！
Please apologize to Shira!
俺たちが シラに謝るだと？
Apologize to Shira?
こいつ 木ノ葉のくせに
シラの味方をするつもりか？
This guy's from the Hidden Leaf and
he's siding with Shira?!
努力を信じる人の前に
敵も味方もありません！
When you believe
in hard work and perseverance,
it doesn't matter whether
you're a friend or foe!
それより貴様！
どうやって あの谷を！
That’s beside the point!
How’d you get across that chasm?!
僕には 努力という
見えない翼があります！
I have invisible wings known
as perseverance!
((うお～っ!!
(でやぁ～！))
努力は時に 不可能を可能にする
無限の翼となるんです。
Sometimes, perseverance...
will turn into infinite wings that
make the impossible possible!
キミたちが謝るまで
僕の怒りはおさまりません！
Until you apologize to Shira,
my rage will not subside!
好きにさせるか。
Like hell we will!
お前の弱点はわかってる。
We know your weakness!
風遁 砂塵旋風。
Wind Style!
Sandstorm Hurricane!
あっ。
セイヤー！
うわっ！
クッ 幻術。
This is genjutsu!
お前はシラと同じ体術特化型だ。
Like Shira, you only specialize
in taijutsu.
なら その弱点をつくまで。
So we'll just capitalize
on your weaknesses!
卑怯です！
正々堂々と 戦ってください。
That's cowardly!
Please fight me fair and square!
ぐっ うっ！
何が卑怯だ。
忍術を使えないお前が悪いのさ。
What's cowardly?!
It's your fault for not knowing ninjutsu!
《この砂塵旋風の中では➡
Inside the Sandstorm Hurricane,
countless sand particles
collide against each other
無数の砂がぶつかり合って
強力な電磁波を生み出す。
and create powerful
electro-magnetic waves.
そして
中に閉じ込められた人間は➡
Because of that,
anyone caught inside it will continue
to experience genjutsu.
その影響で 幻影を見続ける》
そろそろとどめだ。
It's about time to finish this!
なに!?
What?!
ネジ。
Neji!
Jeez! Are you crazy
taking on six by yourself?
もう １人で６人相手なんて
無茶なんだから。
テンテン キミたちも
あの谷を越えられたんですね。
Tenten! You two made it
across too!
あんたにできて 私たちに
できないわけないでしょ。
If you made it, isn't it obvious
we would too?!
クソ…。
Damn it...
俺たちはチームだ。
勝手な行動は慎め。
We're a team!
Don't go off on your own!
すみません。
でもどうしても我慢が。
I'm sorry! I just couldn't stand it...
だが こうなってはしかたがない。
Well, we have no choice now.
行くぞ テンテン。
そうこなくっちゃ！
Let's go, Tenten!
That's more like it!
八卦六十四掌。
8 Trigrams...64 Palms!
うわぁ～！
ぐあっ！
はぁ～！
はっ！
なんだこいつら。
めちゃくちゃつえぇぞ。
What’s their deal?
They’re ridiculously strong!
僕にも 今までの借りを
返させてください。
I would like some payback as well!
木ノ葉大烈風！
Great Leaf Whirlwind!
(シラ)待ってくれ リー。
あっ。
Wait, Lee!
もう許してやってくれ。
シラ君。
Please forgive them.
Shira...!
なぜです？
なぜ かばうんです？
Why?
Why would you defend them?!
彼らはキミを裏切って
ひどい目にあわせたんですよ？
They betrayed you and
put you through hell!
わかってる。
だが それはどうでもいいことだ。
Maybe they did.
But it doesn't matter.
どうでもいいって
どういうことですか？
How can you say
it doesn't matter?!
彼らに 認めてもらえない
俺が悪い。 そういうことだ。
If they won't acknowledge me,
I have only myself to blame.
That's all.
(シラ)言ったはずだ。
生まれのつらさを含めて➡
I already told you.
Whatever my flaws
and misfortunes,
それが俺の人生だと。
this is the life I was born into.
俺は誰も恨んでなどいない。
誰も憎んでもいない。
I'm not bitter, and I bear no grudge.
すべてを含めて俺の人生だ。
Good or bad, this is my life.
すべては 俺の努力が
足りないせいだ。
I have only myself to blame
for the bad
because I didn't work hard enough.
俺は俺の人生を
誰のせいにもしたくない。
I don't want to blame anyone
for the life I have.
シラ君…
キミの努力が足りないなんて…。
Shira...
How can you say
you didn't work hard enough?
うっ うぅ… うわ～ん！
シラ君！
あなたは男の中の男だ。
Shira! You are a man among men!
忍の中の忍だ！
僕は今 最高に感動しています。
The shinobi among shinobi!
I've never been so moved
in my life!
ガイ先生 以来
あなたのようなすばらしい人に➡
Other than Guy Sensei,
I've never met anyone so amazing!
出会ったことがありません！
まったく大げさなんだから。
もらい泣きしそうだったのに➡
You get so carried away.
It was really touching,
until you ruined the mood.
引っ込んだわ。
フッ。
これを持っていってくれ。
これでどちらかの１チームは➡
Take this.
This way, at least one of
our teams will pass.
合格できるはずだ。
えっ。
まったく
どこまでお人好しなのよ。
Damn it... Must you be so kind?
つきあわされる身にも
なってほしいわね。
Put yourself in our shoes, will you?
ごめんなさい！
なんであんたが謝んのよ。
Sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
あっ！ そうでした。
You're right.
だが これを受け取ったら
お前たちは。
But if you take this,
what about you guys...?
俺たちの分は
自分たちで何とかする。
We'll figure something out.
どうしてそこまでする。
我愛羅のためか？
Why would you go so far?
Is it all for Lord Gaara?
あいつは前まで
誰でも殺す残忍な忍だった。
Until recently, he was
a brutal shinobi who'd kill anyone.
それが簡単に変わるかよ。
People don't change so easily!
それはわかっている。
だが 我愛羅様は俺と同じだ。
I realize that.
But Lord Gaara and I
are the same...
そう思ったんだ。
That's what I believe.
(シラ)一緒に修業をしていて
よくわかる。
I can tell from training with him.
我愛羅様は 悔やんでいる
今までの行いを。
Lord Gaara bitterly regrets
his past actions.
そして それが
簡単に償えるものでないことも➡
And he knows that atonement
won't come easy.
よく知っておられる。
だが それでも我愛羅様は
前に進もうとしている。
And yet, Lord Gaara keeps
pushing forward.
人がどう思おうと
努力し続けることが➡
Because despite what
people think of him...
he believes that persevering
is the best thing to do right now.
今の自分にできるベストだと
信じているからだ。
今の自分は問題じゃない。
I don't care about
who I am right now...
未来の自分が恥ずかしくなければ
それでいい。
As long as I'm not ashamed of
the man I am in the future.
うわぁ～。
キミは なんていいことを言うんだ。
Oh, the words that come out
of your mouth!
そうです。 未来の自分が
恥ずかしくなければ➡
You're absolutely right!
What counts is the man
that you are in the future!
それでいいんです。
はいはい。
Okay, okay...
We heard you, pipe down!
わかったから ちょっと黙ってて。
それは 受け取れない。
We... can't accept that.
えっ？
おい お前たちの巻物を。
Hey, give him your scroll.
どうして？
Why?!
俺たちにだってプライドがあるんだよ。
We have our pride too.
今の戦いは 俺たちの負けだ。
We lost this battle.
だから 巻物は渡す。
So we're handing you our scroll.
だが 俺たちだって
このまま終わるつもりはない。
But we're not about
to give up just yet.
自分たちの巻物は
他の連中から奪ってみせる。
We’ll prove it by obtaining the scrolls
from the other teams.
行くぞ。
Let's go!
どうして 彼らは…。
Why did they...?
やつらも未来に恥じない自分を
見つける気になったということだ。
They realized that they don’t want to
be ashamed of themselves in the future.
(リー)シラ君！
あっ。
Shira!
あの ありがとうございました。
Um...
Thank you.
あんたたちのおかげで➡
Thanks to you, it looks like Shira will
have a place in the Hidden Sand.
砂隠れにも シラの居場所が
出来るかもしれないわ。
俺たちの力ではない。
We didn't do anything.
シラ自身の力と
うちの体術バカのおかげだ。
Shira did it with his own strength and
a little help from our taijutsu-idiot.
あいつ まっすぐで
ちょっとシラに似てるかも。
He’s very honest...
He might be a little like our Shira.
えっ それは
あの変な服も髪形もまゆ毛も…。
Uh, I don't think so.
His weird clothes, his hair,
or his eyebrows...
絶対に似てない。
They're not alike at all!
そうね あいつは
ナルトに次ぐバカだから。
That’s true... He’s right up there
with Naruto in stupidity.
ナルト？
うちの里の忍だ。
Naruto?
A shinobi from our village.
He’s on a journey right now.
今は 旅に出ているがな。
そういえば 聞いたことがある。
We’ve heard of him.
我愛羅様の気持を変えた
忍がいるって。
Lord Gaara speaks of a shinobi
who changed him.
それが 確かナルト。
I'm sure the name was Naruto.
あいつ 今頃 何をやっているか。
I wonder what he's up to now?
あっ。
うお～！
ネジ テンテン！
Neji... Tenten...
これは 二次試験とは
まったく関係ないことですが➡
This has nothing to do
with the Second Exam...
お願いがあります。
But I have a favor to ask.
あちゃ～ やっぱり言いだしたか。
Uh-oh... Here we go...
(２人)ん？
僕は あのときのような思いは
二度としたくない。
I never want to go through
something like last time!
《サスケ君は 僕がかなわなかった
あの砂の我愛羅と。
Sasuke beat Gaara of the Sand
against whom I was no match...
そして ナルト君は➡
And Naruto beat Neji
whom I longed to defeat...
僕が倒したいと願い続けた
あのネジを…。
なんでだ なんで こんなに…》
Why? Why does it always
turn out like this?
どうせ 止めたって
聞かないんだろ？
You wouldn't have listened to us
even if we tried to stop you, right?
はい！
Right!
シラ君 僕はキミと戦ってみたい。
Shira! I want to fight you!
同じ体術を
きわめる者同士として➡
Because we both seek
to master taijutsu, please fight me!
僕と戦ってください。
もし戦えるなら
僕は この中忍試験で➡
If I can face you in battle,
I'll have no regrets from
these Chunin Exams!
思い残すことはありません！
いいだろう 望むところだ リー。
Fine with me, Lee.
俺も内心
キミとずっと戦ってみたかった。
To be honest,
I've wanted to fight you!
nando tatakitsukerarete mo
No matter how many times I get beat down
akiramerareru wake nado wanaku genten kaiki
I can't give up, so I go back to my basics
genjitsu to wa baibai shite
I wish we could say bye-bye to this reality
mukashi mitai ni waiwai shitai keredo
And have fun like we used to
sou mo ikanai nara kirihiraite mirya ii
But it doesn't work that way,
so let's carve out our own paths
nokori wazuka no shouki torimodoshite
I'll make you get back the little sanity you have left
me no mae no tobira kojiakete miseru
And then tear down the door in front of you
itsudemo sou nanda
That's the way it is
wasuregachina koto ga
The things you tend to forget
nani yori mo taisetsuna koto datte
Are the things that are the most important
nani ga machiukete iyou to kamawanai
I don't care what lies ahead
ame nimo makezu yami o terasu
The rain won't stop me from lighting up the darkness
kono kyoujin na kokoro ga areba
As long as I have this strong spirit
kono toki kono basho ni tsudoishi nakamatachi
Friends who gather at this time, at this place
mawari tsudzukeru sekai nanbitotari
The world keeps spinning, No one can stop it
tomo tomeru koto wa dekinai yo
Shira! I will show you
how serious I am!
This is my last fight.
Last?
Lee, it’s all because of you,
that I can be a shinobi.
I’m grateful to you.
It might have been your fists
that changed Lord Gaara.
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Ultimate"
Let me express my gratitude
to you with my seriousness!